this tutorial is about floating planes
本教程是关于浮动飞机的
这是一个例子，这些是飞机
this tutorial is about floating planes
so here's an example these are planes
在页面上方浮动
页面，您可以使用它们
so here's an example these are planes
that float above the page parallel with
这样，以页面为基础，
浮在它上面的飞机，或者你可以
that float above the page parallel with
the page and you can either use them
像这样用它的页面
背景和水上飞机
the page and you can either use them
like this with the page as a base and
从中走出来，所以我有一个
这里有几个例子
like this with the page as a base and
the plane floating above it or you can
行动这里是一架漂浮的飞机的翅膀
浮动平面和头部
the plane floating above it or you can
use it like this with the pages of
泰勒是可以跟随他们的加法
艾滋病教程中的另一个例子是
use it like this with the pages of
backgrounds and the floating plane
这个熊头在这里，所以面对
熊是水上飞机，所以我只是
backgrounds and the floating plane
coming forward from it so I've got a
告诉你如何做这些之一
他们是如何工作的
coming forward from it so I've got a
couple of examples here showing it in
平行折叠
教程六，您添加了两个平行四边形
couple of examples here showing it in
action here's a floating plane the wings
教程五对此进行了介绍
然后将浮动平面贴在
action here's a floating plane the wings
of the floating plane and the head and
最佳
从基础表开始，这只是一个
of the floating plane and the head and
Taylor are additions you can follow them
简单的A4卡对折
真的完全折皱，然后
Taylor are additions you can follow them
up in tutorial AIDS the other example is
另一张不太大的卡
像这样折成两半
up in tutorial AIDS the other example is
this bear head here so the face of the
再次像往常一样折痕
彻底，然后在外边缘
this bear head here so the face of the
bear is the floating plane so I just
折叠两个粘贴片，然后将它们
大约半英寸宽或一个
bear is the floating plane so I just
show you how to make one of these this
厘米粗体，靠在自己身上
然后您实际上可以将其折叠
show you how to make one of these this
is how they work you start with a
他们一个人，所以在这里，它是一个
一张带有三个平行折痕的卡片
is how they work you start with a
parallel fold this is covered in
他们或多或少地削减了三成
相同的部分，无需
parallel fold this is covered in
tutorial six you add two parallelograms
测量你只想要三条
他们是三个
tutorial six you add two parallelograms
to it this is covered in tutorial five
将第一个粘贴在
脊椎这是平行折叠，所以我们
to it this is covered in tutorial five
and then you stick the floating plane on
用胶水将胶水粘在一个标签胶上
它非常接近脊椎
and then you stick the floating plane on
top
一厘米或一厘米
确保粘合标签没有
start with a base sheet this is just a
穿过脊椎，然后将胶水涂在
其他标签
start with a base sheet this is just a
simple piece of a4 card folded in half
折叠整个底座关闭，所以这是一个
平行折叠现在您想要更多
simple piece of a4 card folded in half
crease really thoroughly and you take
每边一个平行四边形
让他们找到自己的自然位置
crease really thoroughly and you take
another piece of card not too big
粘上一端，使折痕齐平
与平行线的范围
another piece of card not too big
something like this fold it in half
折叠在那里完全齐平，然后
你把胶水放在另一端，如果
something like this fold it in half
again as always crease it really
您将其折叠到关闭位置并
所以它处于关闭位置
again as always crease it really
thoroughly and then on the outer edges
然后关闭底座，这样就可以
你一个平行四边形从
thoroughly and then on the outer edges
fold two glueing tabs so then they are
如果您愿意，可以平行折叠
在上面贴一张卡片
fold two glueing tabs so then they are
about half an inch wide or one
会像漂浮的飞机一样工作
一侧只是平面图像
about half an inch wide or one
centimeter bold and back on themselves
如果我们要建立另一个
平行四边形到另一边，所以
centimeter bold and back on themselves
and then you can actually fold it with
再次，你做完全一样的事情
粘在一个标签上，将其与
and then you can actually fold it with
them singly so here we have it it's one
顶部的折痕折叠成
平仓
them singly so here we have it it's one
piece of card with three parallel folds
将胶水放在另一个选项卡上，然后关闭
它下来
piece of card with three parallel folds
they cut it into three more or less
所以你有它，你有
水货手机在中间
they cut it into three more or less
identical pieces there's no need to
现在平行四边形就可以了
在上面再贴另一块
identical pieces there's no need to
measure you just want three strips so
这张卡被弄皱了
已经，所以您只需确保
measure you just want three strips so
here they are you have three like this
卡上的中央折痕进入
与主要的那条山脊齐平
here they are you have three like this
stick the first one down spanning the
一块不必对称
我做了对称的作品，但是一旦我
stick the first one down spanning the
spine this is the parallel fold so we
可以缩短任何形状的时间
喜欢，他们把胶水放在小
spine this is the parallel fold so we
take the glue look glue on one tab glue
顶部的表面就坐在那里
确保他们的折痕来自
take the glue look glue on one tab glue
it fairly close to the spine just about
墙壁上肯定是假人
卡太大了
it fairly close to the spine just about
a centimetre out or one centimetre out
出来，所以你可以使用这些东西
只是修剪一下，但一部分
a centimetre out or one centimetre out
make sure the the gluing tab doesn't
设计弹出窗口可以解决哪里
他们是一块去的地方
make sure the the gluing tab doesn't
cross the spine then put glue on the
当它关闭时，有一个
沟渠在这里你可以建在那里
cross the spine then put glue on the
other tab
您可以在下面建造的沟渠
并在侧面，所以你可以建立
fold the whole base closed so this is a
其他弹出式窗口也可以
这四个四个支柱
fold the whole base closed so this is a
parallel fold now you want to more
整个弹出窗口都建立在您身上
你能把东西粘在上面吗
parallel fold now you want to more
parallelograms one on each side so to
他们坚持下去，所以这
产生大量的沟渠，
parallelograms one on each side so to
get them to find their natural position
您可以在所有基础上构建的飞机
在介绍中解释
get them to find their natural position
glue one end so that the crease is flush
教程1还有另一种方法
建立他们正在建立他们
glue one end so that the crease is flush
with the with the reach of the parallel
到V形折叠上，所以在这种情况下，这是一个
v-fold这在教程2中有解释
with the with the reach of the parallel
folds absolutely flush there and then
然后有两个平行四边形
您可以在每一侧贴上浮动
folds absolutely flush there and then
you put glue on the other end and now if
飞机到那些，所以将在这里
这是一张有折痕的卡片
you put glue on the other end and now if
you fold it into its closed position and
在中间，您只需确保
这种折痕与
you fold it into its closed position and
so with it in its closed position
沟渠
所以它找到了自然的黏附
so with it in its closed position
you then close the base so this gives
位置
还有第三种方法可以提高
you then close the base so this gives
you one parallelogram coming off the
页面中间的一个平面
这样，在这种情况下，您将建立
you one parallelogram coming off the
parallel fold if you want you could
每边各出两个平行四边形
这些将这些牢固地固定在适当的位置
parallel fold if you want you could
stick a piece of card on there that that
两个三角形，每个都是
他们两个45度角，让
stick a piece of card on there that that
would work as a floating plane just on
他们两个互相平衡，所以他们
打开时彼此拉扯
would work as a floating plane just on
one side just the flat image in this
并关闭引发该问题的页面
保持刚性，然后建立
one side just the flat image in this
case we're going to build another
我将向您展示平行四边形
书中的一些例子
case we're going to build another
parallelogram onto the other side so
浮动飞机在行动，所以这是一个
非常漂亮的书阿拉丁和他的
parallelogram onto the other side so
again you do exactly the same thing put
魔术灯，全都漂浮着
飞机，如果你看着它结束
again you do exactly the same thing put
glue on one tab glue it flush with the
中央平行折线略
在这种情况下修改，但无论如何在那里
glue on one tab glue it flush with the
crease at the top fold it into its
我们就是，我们有一系列的
所有与飞机平行漂浮的飞机
crease at the top fold it into its
closed position
第二个是这个总和
塔拉伦敦再次这只是
closed position
put glue on the other tab and then shut
浮动飞机，这是那本书
与你与建筑物的背景
put glue on the other tab and then shut
it down
从它出来第三
这是戴维的一些Appleby形状
so there you have it you've got the the
Pellom和这里的最后一个是
在这种情况下的浮动平面
so there you have it you've got the the
parallel phone in the middle to
这些被用来拉起这些
外面的东西，如果你看着它的末端
parallel phone in the middle to
parallelograms coming off it now you can
在上面，您可以看到平行折叠
中间和两个两块
parallelograms coming off it now you can
stick another another piece on top so
两端分别支撑着两条腿
飞机这是一个微小的变化
stick another another piece on top so
here's piece of card thoroughly creased
这是龙，这是相当
基于的惊人构造
here's piece of card thoroughly creased
already so you just make sure that this
在此的中央结构
模型是一个平行的折叠，但它是
already so you just make sure that this
central crease on the card goes into
不对称的平行折叠，因此
整个东西都倾斜了
central crease on the card goes into
flush with that Ridge on the on the main
每一个都有一个平行四边形
它的侧面，然后这是鼻子
flush with that Ridge on the on the main
piece it doesn't have to be symmetrical
实际上是弯曲的形状
在教程13中，我想
piece it doesn't have to be symmetrical
I made a symmetrical piece but once I
告诉你是海伦轰炸机丛林时代
从这两只动物开始
I made a symmetrical piece but once I
could be shorter longer any shape you
它们都基于浮动飞机
长颈鹿的身体和
could be shorter longer any shape you
like and they put the glue on the small
他们都漂浮的大象
飞机并在它们下面建造大象
like and they put the glue on the small
surfaces on the top sit it on there make
头，这是弯曲的形状，这是
教程13和这只长颈鹿的脖子
surfaces on the top sit it on there make
sure their crease is in the gully from
是不对称的V形折叠
那是教程4，所以如果我们看这些
sure their crease is in the gully from
the walls it's sure this is a dummy I
您可以看到它们的制作方式
它的V型折叠抬起平行四边形，
the walls it's sure this is a dummy I
made a bit too big the card is sticking
在这种情况下，平行四边形是
只在你的另一侧
made a bit too big the card is sticking
out so you could either use these things
有一个支持另一个的标签
浮动索赔的一面，
out so you could either use these things
just to trim it down but part of
最后的另一个很好的例子
这本书的就是这个犀牛
just to trim it down but part of
designing pop-ups is working out where
所以犀牛实际上是内置的
三个阶段，您有第一个插件
designing pop-ups is working out where
they're where the piece is going to go
浮动飞机是犀牛的身体
用它的腿
they're where the piece is going to go
when it's closed and so it is there's a
第二个浮动平面是
犀牛耳朵第三步
when it's closed and so it is there's a
gully here you can build into there's
是犀牛的鼻子，这又是
这是弯曲的形状这是教程
gully here you can build into there's
gullies underneath that you can build
13，然后是犀牛
号角，如果我们看看这些浮动
gullies underneath that you can build
into and on the side so you can build
飞机这是一个平行的第一个
每边折叠一个平行四边形
into and on the side so you can build
other pop-ups onto those you've also got
第二个是V形折叠，因此您可以
看到这是V折的区别
other pop-ups onto those you've also got
these four four pillars that are that
他们之间他们给了不同
闭合时动作，V形折叠
these four four pillars that are that
the whole pop up is is built on and you
类型使头部上下移动
平行折叠类型它只是上升和
the whole pop up is is built on and you
can you can stick pieces onto those so
垂直向下，所以如果我们看这个
你会看到犀牛头
can you can stick pieces onto those so
that they stick forward so this
在页面打开时向您靠拢
所以我想告诉你的最后一行是
that they stick forward so this
generates a whole wealth of gullies and
这本惊人的书《勇敢传说》
所有者，这样我想展示的那个
generates a whole wealth of gullies and
planes that you can build on all that is
你是这个惊人的传播，这
桌子桌子实际上是一个
planes that you can build on all that is
explained in the introduction in
在飞机上，如果我们看看它的背面
你会看到桌子的样子
explained in the introduction in
tutorial 1 there's another way of
支持这是45度中的两个
折两个三角形折
tutorial 1 there's another way of
building them which is building them
使中央和
支柱保持它到达，这是这个
building them which is building them
onto a v-fold so in this case this is a
是一本非常了不起的书，这真的
我们完成之前的杰作
onto a v-fold so in this case this is a
v-fold this is explained in tutorial 2
只是想告诉你如何变化
这些东西，所以这是你的基础
v-fold this is explained in tutorial 2
and then it has two parallelograms one
这是脊椎褶皱，这是你的
横跨脊柱的平行折叠
and then it has two parallelograms one
on each side you can stick a floating
那么你不必再做
平行四边形与我的尺寸完全相同
on each side you can stick a floating
plane onto those so that would be here
刚刚在我制作的示例中向您展示了
你可以把它更长一些
plane onto those so that would be here
it is piece of cards with a crease in
可以在这里另辟leg径
另一个在这里，然后
it is piece of cards with a crease in
the middle you just make sure that this
浮动飞机会再次像这样
当然，您必须确保
the middle you just make sure that this
this crease is is lined up with that
底座足够长，所以不会
折叠时伸出，然后
this crease is is lined up with that
gully
重要的是
这条腿和这条腿之间的长度
gully
so it finds its natural sticking
这个长度长度a与这里相同
从山脊到这里
so it finds its natural sticking
position
在此连接的长度也是
腿这个这个高度这个是B这个
there's a third way of actually raising
需要匹配这个高度
初始平行折叠，这是长度B
there's a third way of actually raising
a plane in the middle of the page that's
另一个变化是您的基础
脊椎板在这里建造
a plane in the middle of the page that's
this way so in this case you would build
将平行线折叠到上面然后
其实并不一定要经常
this way so in this case you would build
out two parallelograms one on each side
平行四边形可以做不对称
平行折叠到上面，所以你可能会上升
out two parallelograms one on each side
this is held firmly in place by these
像这样，这样下去
所以在这种情况下，这就是
this is held firmly in place by these
two triangles each of these is just
你在工作，正在测量
到这里，就是这个长度再加上这个
two triangles each of these is just
their two 45-degree angles and let the
长度必须等于这个长度加上这个
长度，这是不对称的平行
their two 45-degree angles and let the
two of them balance each other so they
教程六中介绍的折叠
而另一边则不必
two of them balance each other so they
pull against each other so as you open
与此相同
可能是您知道类似
pull against each other so as you open
and close the page that raises that
这样，以这种方式浮动
您可以建立在其上的飞机可以
and close the page that raises that
keeps it rigid then you build the
实际上并不与之平行
基础，但有些人知道
keeps it rigid then you build the
parallelograms onto it now I'll show you
有点不同的是
我刚刚绘制的图表，以便您可以
parallelograms onto it now I'll show you
a few examples from books of the the
明白我所解释的一切
今天在本教程中
a few examples from books of the the
floating plane in action so this is a
在这本书的弹出式设计中，
纸力学
floating plane in action so this is a
very beautiful book Aladdin and his
您